

Summary

Passionate n' well-qualified mobile engineer with advanced skills on Flutter. Studying Agile, Clean Architecture, SOLID, TDD, Design Patterns and Refactoring. I'm committed to the best way to produce high-quality softwares following good principles and techniques. I have more than 3 years of related experience with software development.

Favorite technologies



Employment history

Mobile developer at Megaleios June 2021 - Present

Mobile developer at Bean Softwares
March 2021 - June 2021

Mobile developer at Thalamus Digital July 2020 - June 2021

Mobile developer at MFIT Personal January 2020 - May 2020

Education

Computer Science at Univali February 2020 - Present

English at KNN Idiomas September 2020 - Present

Projects

Entrepreneur at iCut May 2021 - Present A barber appointment app.

Voluntary coding instructor May 2021 - Present Teaching some friends how to code.

Entrepreneur at StudentPlus August 2018 - April 2021 A study planner based on the Pomodoro technique.

Details

Itajaí, SC, Brazil contact@lucasbatista.me

Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

WhatsApp

Website

Skills

TDD

UI/UX Design

DevOps

UML

Design Patterns

SOLID

Clean Architecture

Agile

Languages

English

Hobbies

Hackathons, pair programming, teaching, code kata and reading.